Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 1: Boxes 1-63
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 1: Boxes 1-63
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Communist influence in the CIO Convention, 1941; Publication (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: The cost of living and wages, 1941; Publication (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: CIO's 1940 legislative program for jobs, security and peace., Publication (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: CIO's tax program, tax wealth, not wages, 1941; Publication (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Keep wages free for a free America!: the case against wage freezing, 1941; Publication (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: The C.I.O. convention and national unity, 1941; Publication (Box 44, Folder 5)
    Author: Roy Hudson
  - Item 7: The Right to strike: keystone of liberty, 1941; Publication (Box 44, Folder 5)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Labor's political future in the United States by Sidney Hillman, 1942; Publication (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: CIO servicemen's manual, 1944; Publication (Box 44, Folder 6)
    Author: Dallas Johnson
  - Item 3: Free labor means victory: slave labor means defeat, 1941; Publication (Box 44, Folder 6)
    Notes: Publication no.60. Copy 2
  - Item 4: The C.I.O. convention and national unity, 1941; Publication (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Your war job with Congress., 1943; Publication (Box 44, Folder 6)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: CIO Attorneys for National Unions - Memos, 1943-1944 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: National and International Presidents and Organizing Committees, Regional Directors, State and Local Councils, 1943; Publication (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: War Manpower Commission, 1942; Publication (Box 44, Folder 7)
    Notes: RESTRICTED
  - Item 4: All out for victory: CIO program adopted in Cleveland, May, 1943., Publication (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Back bullets with ballots, 1913; Publication (Box 44, Folder 7)
    Author: Sidney Hillman
  - Item 6: Keeping score to win the war: the record of Congress and what to do about it., 1943; Publication (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Security for the people, Publication (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Taxes to win: Text and discussion of CIO's 1943 victory tax program, adopted at the CIO Executive Board meeting, February., Publication (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: The road to victory: CIO's 1943 legislative program, Publication (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: You can have decent wages and working conditions if you go after them: here's how, 1940; Publication (Box 44, Folder 7)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: A new movement in adult education, 1944; Publication (Box 44, Folder 8)
    Author: Helen Sorenson & Milo Lathrop
  - Item 2: A society of free men, 1944; Publication (Box 44, Folder 8)
    Author: Bernard J. Sheil
  - Item 3: How high is up?: the truth about the cost of living, 1944; Publication (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Labor's good neighbor policy: address, Publication (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: The union in wartime: What it can do for you and your country, 1944; Publication (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Wages now and after V-E Day, 1945; Publication (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Your war job with Congress, 1943; Publication (Box 44, Folder 8)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: 5,000,000 jobs in world trade, the promise of Bretton Woods, 1944; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: First aid lay-offs, 1945; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Memorandum for: All CIO Attorneys, 1945; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Memorandum for: General Counsels of CIO unions, 1945; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: The Story of scapegoats in history, -They got the blame- -comic book, Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: A Radio forum conducted by the American Federation of Labor on: should the Wagner Act be amended?, 1947; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: Don't let Congress put the clock back., Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Security for the people, 1940; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: Shortage of labor?: don't be fooled: here are the facts!, 1939; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 10: You can have decent wages and working conditions if you go after them: here's how., 1940; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: State Industrial Union Councils (36), Affiliated with the Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1946; Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Testimony of James B. Carey, Sec. Treasurer, CIO, 1946; Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Meyer Bernstein, CIO Veteran's Rep., Back dating seniority on Veteran's promotions, 1947; Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Testimony of Kermit Eby, Director of Ed. And Research, 1947; Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Forward together, 1948; Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Twelve questions about the CIO for telephone workers, 1948; Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Are you going to be drafted?: your rights and duties under the 1948 selective service, Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: How can we best preserve our human and natural resources?, 1948; Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: The path we must follow leads neither to right nor left, 1948; Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Statement of the Congress of Industrial Organizations, presented by Mrs. Katherine Pollak Ellickson, 1949; Publication (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Testimony of James B. Carey, Sec. Treasurer, CIO, 1949; Publication (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Text of letter from CIO General Counsel Arthur J. Goldberg to Sen. Elbert Thomas, 1949; Publication (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: The double standard in steel, 1949; Publication (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Vote CIO, 1949; Publication (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: A national economic policy for 1949, Publication (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: Where is the CIO going?: A program for militant trade unionism, 1949; Publication (Box 44, Folder 13)
    Author: George Morris
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: A woman's guide to political action, 1944; Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
    Author: Congress of Industrial Organizations (U.S.). Political Action Committee
  - Item 2: Bretton Woods is no mystery, 1945; Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Every worker a voter, 1944; Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1
  - Item 4: Four men speak about jobs for all, 1944; Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
    Author: Congress of Industrial Organizations (U.S.). Political Action Committee.
  - Item 5: If inflation comes, 1945; Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Jobs for all after the war, 1944; Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: PAC radio handbook, 1946; Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Radio handbook., 1944; Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Speakers manual, 1944; Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: The answer is full employment, 1946; Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: The need for action, 1943; Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: The people's program for 1944, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: The people's program for 1946, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: The story of Dumbarton Oaks: Angels could do it better, 1944; Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: There's no place like home: if you can get one, 1946; Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: This is your America, 1944; Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: What every canvasser should know, 1944; Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: What every voter should know and do in 1946, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: When a worker needs a friend, 1946; Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: As goes reconversion so goes our future, Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Statement of Sidney Hillman, before the Special Comm. Of the House to investigate campaign expenditures, 1944; Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Ten million of us, 1945; Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Turn around and vote!, Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: What happens to your PAC dollar, Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: What is the P.A.C.?, Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Where your PAC dollar goes, Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Every worker a voter, 1944; Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.2 (2 copies)
  - Item 9: Radio handbook., 1944; Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Speakers manual, 1944; Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: The story of Dumbarton Oaks: Angels could do it better, 1944; Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: This is your America, 1944; Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: What every canvasser should know, 1944; Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: CIO Policy Statement on workmen's compensation brief, 1950; Publication (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: CIO's 1950 Convention resolution on improving Educational opportunities for children, Publication (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: The C.I.O. today, 1950; Publication (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: What is ahead of labor, 1950; Publication (Box 45, Folder 3)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Labor and the National Emergency, text of a labor day address by Pres. Philip Murray, 1951; Publication (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Oil for education, 1951; Publication (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Statement of behalf of the CIOpresented by Stanley H. Ruttenberg, 1951; Publication (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Spotlight on mobilization, 1951; Publication (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Taft-Hartley: a CIO appraisal, 1952; Publication (Box 45, Folder 4)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Annual report by Pres. Philip Murray, 14th Constitutional Convention, 1952; Publication (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: CIO calls for a strengthened platform for republican party, 1952; Publication (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: CIO World Affairs Bulletin, 1952; Publication (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Program, 14th Constitutional Convention, 1952; Publication (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Supplemental report by the Exec. Officers and V. Pres. To the 14th Constitutional Convention of the CIO, 1952; Publication (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Testimony of James B. Carey, Sec. Treasurer, CIO, 1952; Publication (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: The Blessings of freedom, Publication (Box 45, Folder 5)
    Author: Francis J. Haas
  - Item 8: Letter from James B. Carey, 1952; Publication (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Supplementary Report of Resolutions Committee: Fourteenth Constitutional Convention of the Congress of Industrial Organizations, Atlantic City, N.J., December 1-5, 1952., Publication (Box 45, Folder 5)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: CIO Economic Committee expresses concern at recent trends and actions of Administration and Congress, 1953; Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Memorandum, sent to Pres. Helstein by CIO Exec. V. Pres., 1953; Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Now is the time, Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Build democracy in the classroom, 1953; Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: A new minimum wage for 1955!, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: CIO's welfare code, 1954; Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
    Notes: Page from manual
  - Item 3: Partners in production, Farmers and CIO, 1954; Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Report on CIO Radio Program, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: letter to Congressman Hope from the CIO, 1954; Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: North and south of the border: Western Hemisphere labor, united for victory, 1944; Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: We saw Israel; a report of a visit by three AFL union officials, 1954; Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: American labor, this is how you can fight for democracy, Publication (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Memo on taxes, 1955; Publication (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: CIO, 1935-1955; industrial democracy in action, Publication (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: The impact of automation and the workers, 1955; Publication (Box 45, Folder 8)
    Author: Ted F. Silvey
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Howard replies to council's charge committee is illegal, Publication (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Organizational leaflets, Publication (Box 45, Folder 9)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: 15-cent bus fare sought by 9 lines, Publication (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: 55 CIO honor goes to Mrs. Roosevelt, Publication (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Automation links industry, labor, Publication (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: CIO ADA hit Fulbright bill on natural gas, 1955; Publication (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: CIO aids flood areas, Publication (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: CIO social unit looks to merger, Publication (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: CIO warns locals on red infiltration, Publication (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Effect of automation probed, Publication (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: Experts divided on automation, Publication (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: Quill excoriates new labor group, 1955-1956 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Item 11: Reuther advises on world policy, Publication (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Item 12: Reuther against Brown, Publication (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Item 13: Reuther assails wage floor plan, Publication (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Item 14: Reuther expects 4-day week by '65, Publication (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Item 15: The automation hearings, Publication (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Item 16: Union designates political chiefs, Publication (Box 45, Folder 10)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Memo from PAC, 1947-1950 (Box 45, Folder 11)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: C.I.O. Organizers Bulletin, 1937; Publication (Box 45, Folder 12)
    Notes: v. 1 no. 8-10 (Sept.-Dec., 1937)
  - Item 2: How the union works, Publication (Box 45, Folder 12)
    Notes: organizing pamphlet
  - Item 3: I'm kind of puzzled, Publication (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Labor and religion together, Publication (Box 45, Folder 12)
    Author: John G. Ramsay
  - Item 5: Love the neighbor, Publication (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: The Church and the CIO together, Publication (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: The churches and brotherhood, Publication (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: The Community depends on WAGES, Publication (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Item 9: Election procedures under the National Labor Relations Act, 1946; Publication (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Item 10: Memo from PAC, 1948; Publication (Box 45, Folder 12)
    Notes: Victory edition v.2, no. 15, 1948
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: $27.62 lost or stolen, Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Build a stronger PAC, Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Don't let our workers starve, Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Labor and political action after World War I: 1919-1924, 1946; Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Memorandum to the subscribers to PAC material, 1945; Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: Now, Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: Ten million of us earn less than 64 [cents] an hour, Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: The CIO news, 1946; Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
    Notes: August 1946. Unbound
  - Item 9: The PAC is here to stay, 1945; Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 10: The password is: full employment, Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 11: Wake up your congressman for $1, Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 12: What is PAC, Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 13: Why labor is in politics, 1946; Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
    Author: Jack Kroll
  - Item 14: Remember in November, 1946; Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 15: The people's program for 1946, Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 16: The road to freedom; higher basic wages and salaries, 1946; Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 17: There's no place like home: if you can get one, 1946; Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 18: What every voter should know and do in 1946, Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Here we stand, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
    Notes: CIO pamphlet
  - Item 2: How we win, 1948; Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Letter to "International Unions, Regional Directors and State and Local Industrial Union Council", 1947; Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Political action techniques for victory in '48, 1948; Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Poster advertising your right to vote, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Price, 1948; Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Registration data for 1948, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Taft-Hartley and you, 1947; Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Unfinished business, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: We've had enough, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: What about the third party?..., Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: What is PAC, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: What would you do with 25 million?, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: What's cooking Joe?, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: When a worker needs a friend, 1946; Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Taft-Hartley and Farrell Acts, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: This work must go on, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: A look at Truman's record on civil rights, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: Everything we have, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: 81st Congress, a progress report: what Congress did and did not do, with a chart showing the votes of every member of the House and Senate on 15 crucial issues, 1949; Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: An open letter, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Election poster - "Remember November '48", 1948; Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Everything we have, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
    Notes: CIO pamphlet. Copy 2
  - Item 5: King for a day, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: PAC radio handbook, 1946; Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Questions about the battle in Korea, 1950; Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Registration manual, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Keep punching with a buck to PAC, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Labor's stake in civic affairs, 1949; Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: State of the union: a program for liberal America -, 1949; Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: This is PAC, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: What is PAC, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: For ROSES 'round your door, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: How Stalin hopes we will destroy America, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Notes: Comic book
  - Item 3: My daddy is a block worker, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Prices, taxes, rents, wages, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: The CIO news -, 1951; Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Notes: 1951 December. Unbound
  - Item 6: The inside story of your PAC dollar, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: This is PAC, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Letter from CIO, PAC, 1951; Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: The effectiveness of PAC in New Jersey; a comprehensive study of the methods, problems and results obtained in New Jersey during the 1950 Congressional election campaign by the CIO Political Action Committee, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Author: Congress of Industrial Organizations (U.S.). Political Action Committee for New Jersey
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: '52 facts on politics, 1952; Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: For ROSES 'round your door, Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: How to cut your food bill, Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: How to cut your rent, Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: How to get a raise, Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: One managainst millions!, Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Politics is your baby too!, Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: The inside story of your PAC dollar, Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: To get price control and cut your food bill, Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: What is PAC?, Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Who me? In politics?, Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: '52 facts about prices, 1952; Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: '52 facts about taxes., 1952; Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: '52 facts on civil rights., 1952; Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: '52 facts on corruption, 1952; Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: '52 facts on Foreign policy, 1952; Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: '52 facts on Taft-Hartley, 1952; Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Item 18: Adlai Stevenson., 1952; Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: Cartoon/Comic strip - "Marcus Carcass, the Meatball King", Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Item 20: Cartoon/Comic strip - "The Good Old Days", Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Item 21: CIO, PAC election calendar, 1952; Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Item 22: Election poster, Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Item 23: letter to "Friends and Fellow Union Members", 1954; Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: One managainst millions!, Publication (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: The Milwaukee Journal -, 1953; Publication (Box 46, Folder 5)
    Notes: Sunday, Dec. 20, 1953. Newspaper clipping
  - Item 3: What if you are disabled?, Publication (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Roll Call, 1953; Publication (Box 46, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.1:no.1-2 (Feb, Nov 1953)
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), Publication (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: How to save up to $228 a year!, Publication (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Most appeals for funds use pretty girls, Publication (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Some advice to Mr. Fixit, Publication (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: The New Look, Publication (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Throw your buck in the ring, Publication (Box 46, Folder 6)